Privacy Policy
==============

Simplecast is committed to transparency and protecting your privacy.
--------------------------------------------------------------------

Welcome to Simplecast. Simplecast d/b/a Audio Ventures Inc. (“Simplecast”, “we” or “us”) provides supporting services to podcast content creators and owners (“Content Owners”), including but not limited to podcast hosting and a standalone web podcast player (the “Services”).  Simplecast is a wholly owned subsidiary of AdsWizz Inc. This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes the collection and uses of personal data by Simplecast in the delivery of the Services and through the websites hosted on the simplecast.com domain (the “Websites”). This Privacy Policy does not apply to the collection or use of personal data by other services offered by AdsWizz Inc., by platforms that distribute podcasts, or any content-related websites that are not hosted on the simplecast.com domain. Use of the Services and the Websites are governed by this Privacy Policy and the Simplecast Terms and Conditions, where applicable. Content Owners with Simplecast podcast hosting accounts, please also refer to the Services [Terms and Conditions](https://simplecast.com/terms-conditions?hsLang=en) and [Data Processing Addendum](https://simplecast.com/dpa?hsLang=en) or the business agreement executed between you and Simplecast, as applicable.

For questions about Simplecast’s collection and use of personal data, contact [privacy@adswizz.com](mailto:privacy@adswizz.com). Changes to this Privacy Policy will be at our discretion.  We will provide notice of such changes as described in the “Amendments and Changes to this Privacy Policy” 

### 1\. Personal Data Collected by Simplecast.

Clients of the Services: We collect data from or about Content Owners who inquire about or sign up for a Simplecast account (individually and collectively, the “Client”), or otherwise engage us for the business of hosting the delivery of the Client podcasts and related Services.

When a Client contacts us for information about or sign up for a free or paid account for Simplecast hosting services, we collect information from or about the Client to conduct that business relationship. Such information may constitute personal data under certain laws. The types of information may include data such as the name of a Client representative, contact information such as email address, postal address, and billing information.

We use this information:

* To operate and make available the Services to and for the benefit of the Client;
* For billing and fraud prevention;
* To analyze the use of the Services and for internal market research to improve and grow our business;
* To communicate with you in response to your inquiries and/or about your account;
* To deliver (via email, chat, SMS, push notifications, or otherwise) product and service updates, transactional information, administrative notices, special events, contests, marketing notifications, offers and communications relevant to your use of the Services, with your consent when required under applicable law;
* To provide you with customer support for the Services and to fulfill our contract with you;
* To enforce our Agreement including the Simplecast Terms and Conditions, and any other legal rights or obligations, including responding to legal requests; and
* As otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy and the Simplecast Terms and Conditions.

End Users of the Services and the Websites: We also collect certain types of personal data from visitors to the Websites or other end users/listeners of podcasts that Simplecast delivers on behalf of the Client.

The types of data that Simplecast collects about you as an End User include:

* Digital Activity Data, such as IP address, user agent, browser type, device type, cookie data and other website tracking technologies, and
* Country where the website visit or the podcast request emanated, derived from IP address. We do not collect precise geolocation about you without your express consent.

We use this information to:

* Operate and make available the Services and the Websites to users and visitors, including deliver requested episode streams or downloads;
* Maintain, or to investigate or respond to threats to, the security of the Services and the Websites, to troubleshoot problems, and to prevent fraud;
* Analyze the use of the Services and the Websites for performance and market research in order to improve and grow our business;
* Generate reports on content performance, listening activity and other usage for the Client;
* Enforce any terms of use, or other legal rights or obligations, including responding to legal requests or court orders;
* Ensure license compliance, including territorial restrictions where applicable;
* Fulfill Client instructions for monetization and advertising; and
* As otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy.

We aggregate personal data of End Users for the purpose of reporting on Content usage to the Client. The aggregated data is not identifiable to any individual and may be disclosed to other third parties. We maintain the aggregated information in de-identified format, and do not attempt, and contractually restrict other third parties from attempting, to reassociate aggregated information to individuals.

### 2\. Use of Pixels, Cookies, and Tags.

The Websites use cookies, pixels or tags or similar technologies to store the preferences of site visitors and to record session information for various purposes. Some cookies provide essential functions to the performance of the Website. Cookies, pixels or tags may also be used on the Websites to collect or transmit information to service providers and third parties that allow Simplecast or its Clients to track Website traffic, navigation, and overall usage, to determine how to best provide information to visitors, to monitor the effectiveness of our communication of the Services to potential Clients, to customize our newsletter, or to determine and improve the effectiveness of our or our Clients' advertising campaigns.

A Website reflecting the content of a particular Client that is hosted on a subdomain of simplecast.com may contain analytical or advertising cookies, pixels or tags placed by Simplecast for analytical purposes, or directly by the Client for analytics or to measure the effectiveness of the Client’s advertising directing users to the content page. Data collected or transmitted by Client-placed technologies is subject to the Client’s relationships with you as an end user of that Client’s content and with the data recipient. Please see any privacy policy offered by the podcast content owner for more information. Please note that Simplecast does not control the delivery of advertising within the podcast content stream, and advertising cookies on the Websites are independent of advertising that you may hear while listening to any given podcast content.  

You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject non-essential cookies or to notify you when a cookie is set. Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. In addition, you may disable analytical or advertising cookies for a Website through the cookie banner on the Website or the Cookie Settings link in the footer of the page. You may not disable essential cookies.

[View Simplecast’s Cookie Declaration and adjust your cookie preferences](https://simplecast.com/cookie-declaration/?hsLang=en)

Simplecast uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service. Google Analytics uses cookies to help us analyze how visitors use the Simplecast Websites. The information generated by cookies about your use of the Websites (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by a Google server in the United States. Google uses this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the Websites, compiling reports on site activity, and providing other services relating to site activity and Internet usage. You can prevent the storage of data relating to your use of the Simplecast Websites and created via the cookie (including your IP address) by Google, as well as the processing of this data by Google, by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en.). You can obtain additional information on Google Analytics’ collection and processing of data and data privacy and security at the following links: [How Google Uses Information From Sites Or Apps That Use Our Services](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites) and [Analytics Help](https://support.google.com/analytics/topic/2919631).

Note that cookie settings and other technological controls are specific to the browser or device on which such control is implemented. When cookies or other such tags are disabled, we are not able to recognize you when you use a different device to access the Services, and therefore cannot apply the settings from the initial device. You will need to manage your cookies and tag settings as well as any global privacy controls individually on each device or browser with which you access the Services.

Global Privacy Control (GPC) and Do Not Track (DNT) Signals. Global Privacy Controls (“GPC”) and Do Not Track (“DNT”) offered by some web browsers are settings that automatically inform websites of your privacy preferences. When you choose to turn on the GPC/DNT setting in your browser, your browser sends a special signal to websites, analytics companies, ad networks, plug in providers, and/or other web services you encounter while browsing to exercise your privacy rights and stop tracking your activity. You can learn more about and set up GPC  [here](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/#about): [https://globalprivacycontrol.org/#about](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/#about) and set up Do Not Track [here](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/): [http://www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/). We comply with GPC as required under applicable law, but because there is no standardized response to browser DNT signals, the Websites do not respond to such signals.

### 3\. Disclosures and Sharing

**Client Data**. Simplecast may disclose data of Clients to a variety of third party service providers, who work on our behalf and do not have an independent right to use the data. Service providers may include the cloud services hosting environment, our billing platform, security and log monitoring companies, customer service support vendors, and third party marketing platforms and email distributors. We may also share data about Clients with companies affiliated with us, for business or commercial purposes. Simplecast does not sell, rent or trade personal data of Clients to third parties for their own use.

Simplecast may send business communications with pixel tags that enable us to send email messages in a format the recipient can read, and to tell us whether emails have been opened. We also may send business email messages which use or otherwise contain a “click-through URL” that is linked to content on the Websites. When the “click-through URL” is engaged, data identifying the email recipient is collected and used by Simplecast to determine interest in particular topics and to measure the effectiveness of the communications. To avoid this tracking, do not click on text or graphic links in such email communications.

Email Preferences / Opting-Out. Occasionally, Simplecast may send marketing email regarding news, promotions, surveys, updates, or offers related to Simplecast. Recipients who no longer wish to receive marketing emails may choose to opt-out through the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the email. Clients cannot opt-out of email for the purpose of delivering legal notices or Client account changes.

**End Users.** We disclose personal data of end users of the Websites to service providers that host and administer the website technology. We may also disclose personal data of end users of the Websites and the Services to podcast reporting companies, which aggregate such data such data to provide podcast rankings.

The Websites also collect and disclose personal data of end users to the Client through cookies and pixels placed by the Client for service visibility and to support advertising performance and reporting (please read the section above, “Use of Cookies, Pixels and Tags” for more information).

In addition, upon instruction of the Client, we disclose certain device level data such as IP address and user agent, collected by the server’s transmission of content to individual end users, to third party advertising technology providers selected by the Client, in order to facilitate the delivery of advertising for the benefit of the Client. Simplecast is not an advertising technology entity and does not sell or deliver advertising into the content stream. Simplecast does not sell, rent or trade personal data of end users, other than to the extent expressly described in the section “Use of Cookies, Pixels and Tags”.

* From time to time, Simplecast may sponsor a promotion, sweepstakes, or contest on the Simplecast Websites. In such cases users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address, or to answer questions as part of the entry process. In some instances, Simplecast may ask you for permission to transfer such personal information to certain third-party partners. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply, and the sharing of your information to such third party will be with your consent only.

In addition to the above, we may disclose personal data as required or permitted by law, such as:

* to comply with a civil, criminal, or regulatory inquiry, investigation, subpoena, or summons by federal, state, local, or other governmental authorities;
* when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, your safety, or the safety of others;
* to prevent, detect, protect against, or respond to security incidents, identity theft, fraud, harassment, malicious or deceptive activities, or other illegal activity, or preserve the integrity or security of systems;
* to investigate, establish, exercise, prepare for, or defend legal claims; or
* to a successor in interest as a result of the sale of all or substantially all of Simplecast’s assets.

**Links to Third-Party Websites.** Simplecast contains links to third party websites. Simplecast is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of or on other websites. When linking to another website, a user should read the privacy policy stated on that website. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on the Simplecast Websites.

**Notice Regarding the Privacy of Children Under 13.** None of the Services or Websites are directed to use by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect or use personal data from anyone under 13 years of age.

**Information Retention.** Simplecast retains personal data of Clients, to the extent applicable, for the duration of your account with us, and for any subsequent length of time necessary to fulfill legitimate business interests and our legal obligations. Personal data of End Users of the Services and the Websites is retained for the time required to fulfill the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**Security.** Simplecast Accounts are secured by user-created (as applicable) passwords. Simplecast takes precautions to ensure that account information is kept private through reasonable measures such as encryption to protect private information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to such private information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note, however, that Simplecast cannot and does not guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user account information at any time. Users are urged to take precautions to protect their personal data by changing passwords often, using a combination of letters and numbers, and using a secure web browser. For any additional information about the security measures Simplecast uses on the Simplecast Websites, please contact us at [support@simplecast.com](mailto:support@simplecast.com).

**Amendments and Changes to this Privacy Policy.** From time to time, Simplecast may make changes to this Privacy Policy. If we make changes, we will post them on this URL to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A user is bound by any minor changes to the Privacy Policy when she or he uses the the Simplecast Websites after those changes have been posted. If, however, we are going to use a user’s personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on Simplecast for 30 days.

### 4\. Transfer to and Processing of Personal Data in the United States

Simplecast is owned and operated in the United States. Individuals who reside outside the United States, including Clients or End Users of the content delivered by the Services or the Websites, should be aware that personal data collected by the Services or the Websites will be transferred to the United States for processing including retention. The types of Personal Data collected by the Services and the Websites is described in this Privacy Policy and detailed in the tables below. The transfer of such data to the United States is necessary for Simplecast to administer and deliver the Services and for the legitimate business interests of Simplecast operating as a processor for the Client. If you are a resident outside of the United States and you object to the processing of your personal data in the United States for the purposes described herein, please do not use the Simplecast Services or Websites. Data subject requests or inquiries, where applicable by law, can be made by contacting [privacy@adswizz.com](mailto:privacy@adswizz.com).  

### 5\. US State Specific Rights

Simplecast functions as a service provider or processor for personal data of end users of the Services and the Websites other than the main page of simplecast.com. Requests to exercise consumer privacy rights for such end users should be made directly to the Podcast Content Owner, who will direct Simplecast on the nature of the request. Other individuals who are residents of certain U.S. states may have the ability to exercise additional rights and choices regarding their personal data directly with Simplecast. We will take reasonable steps to accommodate your request but may need to verify your identity before doing so, where possible.

1. **_Colorado, Connecticut, Montana, Oregon, Texas, Utah, and Virginia_****.** We set forth in this Policy the categories of personal data we process, the purpose for processing personal data, the categories of personal data shared, and the categories of third parties with whom personal data is shared. Residents of CO, CT, MT OR, TX, UT, and VA have certain privacy rights with respect to this data, as described below. 

**Your Rights** 

**Access Your Information**/**Obtain Your Information/Data Portability** (CO, CT, MT, OR, TX, UT, VA Residents) –You have the right to confirm whether we are processing your personal data and request to access such data, obtain a copy of the personal data previously provided by you to us and, to the extent feasible, in a readily usable format to allow data portability. If you are an Oregon resident, you have the right to request a list of third parties to which Simplecast may have disclosed any personal data.

**Delete Your Information** (CO, CT, MT, OR, TX, UT, VA Residents). You have the Right to request the deletion of your personal data, subject to certain exemptions and exceptions.

**Correct Your Information** (CO, CT, MT, OR, TX, VA Residents). You have the Right to correct the personal data we hold about you.

**Sensitive Data**. Simplecast does not collect or process any sensitive data as defined under CO, CT, MT, OR, TX, VA, or UT law.

**Opt-Out of Sale of Your Personal Data** **and Targeted Advertising** (CO, CT, MT, OR, TX, VA and UT residents) **\-**  Sharing of IP address or mobile ad IDs with third party advertising vendors and certain other targeted advertising practices may constitute a “sale” under definitions set forth in CO, CT, OR, and TX laws. You have the right to opt-out of “Sale” of personal data or from the use of personal data in “Targeted Advertising”, as defined by the applicable state law, using the methods described below, as further described in this Privacy Policy, or the linked Cookie Declaration. Simplecast does not sell personal data to third parties in exchange for monetary compensation. Please note that opting out of “sale” or “targeted advertising” in any of these states will not opt you out of all advertising. You may continue to receive ads that are associated to the context of the content or that otherwise do not use personal data to identify you, either in the content to which you are listening or on third party websites.  

_Cookie Based Opt-Outs for Sale and Targeted Advertising_

Simplecast may use technologies, such as cookies and pixels, in the course of web-based or online advertising, analytics or similar activities that collect or share personal data in a manner that may constitute a “sale” under CO, CT, OR, and TX law or support “targeted advertising” under VA, CO, CT, OR, TX and UT state laws. You may opt out of cookies and pixels set for advertising or analytics using the methods described above in the section, “Use of Cookies, Pixels and Tags”.

**Right to Opt-Out of Profiling in furtherance of legal or similarly significant effects** (CO, CT, VA). Simplecast does not process personal data for the purposes of profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects.

**Right to Appeal** (CO, CT, MT, OR, TX, and VA Residents) – You have the right to appeal our decision relating to your request. You may submit an appeal by contacting privacy@ adswizz.com.

Table 5.1 below describes personal data collected and disclosed in accordance with CO, CT, MT, OR, TX, and VA state law:

|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Category of Personal Data** | **A. Purpose for Collection** | **B. Categories of Third Parties Personal Data is Disclosed To** | **C. Third Parties to whom Personal Data is Sold or Shared for Targeted Advertising** |
| **Registration Data -** This may include name, email address, mailing address, phone number. | **1\. Provide You Services** (process orders; facilitate access to Services, manage your account; send account related communications; respond to inquiries; provide customer service; send information that you requested or agreed to receive such as newsletters);<br><br>**2\. Internal Business Purposes** (provide and improve our services; market research and auditing; understand how service usage; analyze the effectiveness of B2B marketing efforts); <br><br>**3\. Marketing** (to offers, invites to events, and similar information); <br><br>**4\. Administrative**  (investigate and prevent fraud and other illegal activities; detect and troubleshoot technical issues). | **1\. Technology Systems Service Providers** (including web hosts, database hosts, software-as-a-service providers, cloud computing providers, technology maintenance, repair), <br><br>**2\. Customer Service Providers** (agents, email delivery and text messaging vendors), <br><br>**3\. Billing Fulfillment Service Providers**  (payment processors), <br><br>**4.** **Sweepstakes/** **Promotions Vendors**, <br><br>**5\. Simplecast Affiliates** | **1\. Advertising Entities and Analytics Providers**<br><br>**2\. Simplecast Affiliates** |
| **Device Data –**This may include IP address, mobile device ID, other unique ID, device information (device model, operating system version, date and time of access, mobile network information, cookie settings). | **1\. Provide You Services** (facilitate access to the Services; **identify and recognize you across services and devices**); <br><br>**2**. **Internal Business Purposes**  (provide and improve our services; market research and auditing; understand how you use our services, including analyzing trends and usage patterns); <br><br>**3**. **Marketing** (to send you special deals, offers, invites to events, and similar information from us or third parties); <br><br>**4**. **Advertising** (to tailor content, including advertising and listening recommendations, to you on the Services and on other websites and services; to monitor and control the ad delivery, performance and frequency); <br><br>**5**. **Administrative**  (investigate and prevent fraud and other illegal activities; detect and troubleshoot technical issues). | **1\. Technology Systems Service Providers** (including webhosts, database hosts, software-as-a-service providers, cloud computing providers, technology maintenance, repair), <br><br>**2\. Customer Service Providers** (email delivery and text messaging vendors), <br><br>**3****. Third-Party Advertising Entities and Analytics Providers** (analytics companies, marketing agencies), <br><br>**4\. Security Vendors,**<br><br>**5\. Simplecast Affiliates** | **1\. Advertising Entities and Analytics Providers**<br><br>**2\. Simplecast Affiliates** |
| **Geolocation Data –** This may include approximate location at state or region/country level. | **1\. Provide You Services** (facilitate access to the Services; exercise territorial limits where required); <br><br>**2\. Internal Business Purposes** (provide and improve our services; market research and auditing; understand how you use our services, including analyzing trends and usage patterns); <br><br>**3\. Marketing** (to send you offers, invitations to events, and similar information from us or third parties); <br><br>**4\. Advertising** (to tailor advertising, based on your location); <br><br>**5\. Administrative** (investigate and prevent fraud and other illegal activities). | **1\. Technology Systems Service Providers** (including webhosts, database hosts, software-as-a-service providers, cloud computing providers, technology maintenance, repair, security vendors), <br><br>**2\. Customer Service Providers** (email delivery and text messaging vendors), <br><br>**3\. Third-Party Advertising Entities and Analytics Providers**  (analytics companies, marketing agencies), <br><br>**4\. Simplecast Affiliates** | **1\. Advertising Entities and Analytics Providers**<br><br>**2\. Simplecast Affiliates** |

**Exercise Your Rights** 

If you are a Consumer residing in CO, CT, MT, OR, TX, VA, or UT (as defined in each state’s respective law) and would like to exercise your applicable rights as outlined above, please submit your request to privacy@adswizz.com

Authorized Agents Submitting Opt-Out Requests for Sales and Targeted Advertising (CO, CT, OR, and TX Residents Only) - If you are an authorized agent submitting a request to opt out of sales or targeted advertising on behalf of a CO, CT, MT, OR, or TX resident, please submit your request to [privacy@adswizz.com](mailto:privacy@adswizz.com). Please note that the only personal data that Simplecast may disclose that might be considered a sale under these laws is IP address and user agent or the personal data that may be collected and transmitted through cookies or other technologies on the Website subject to an associated browser level opt-out mechanism. If we cannot authenticate that you are authorized to act on the consumer’s behalf or if we cannot authenticate the consumer’s identity against this limited personal data, we may deny the request.

220. **_Nevada_****.** If you are a Nevada resident please note that we do not sell your personal data (or “covered information”) as defined in Nevada S.B. 220.

Nevada residents have the right to know about the collection, sharing, sale, and use of health-related data about them. Simplecast does not collect, share, sell, or use health-related data about consumers, as defined by Nevada S.B.370.

1. **_California_**. Your Rights Under the California Consumer Privacy Act as amended, The following applies only to California residents regarding their personal information, as defined under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018, as amended (the “CCPA”).

Your Rights.

California Consumers (as defined under the CCPA) have the following rights, all subject to the meanings under the CCPA.

* Rights to Know or Access – the rights to request that we disclose to you what personal information we collect, use, disclose, share and sell, including the rights to request that provide to you the categories and specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you;
* Right to Delete – the right to request that we delete certain personal information we collect about you, subject to exceptions specified under the CCPA;
* Right to Correct – the right to request that we correct inaccurate personal information we hold about you;
* Right to Opt-out of sale or sharing – you may opt-out from the sale of your personal information, or from the sharing of your personal information to a third party for cross-context behavioral advertising, and
* Right to Limit the Use and Disclosure of Sensitive Personal Information.

To exercise your rights, please submit your request to privacy@adswizz.com. You must provide enough information to allow us to verify that you are the person about whom we collected personal information, or their authorized agent. You must also describe your request with enough detail that we can understand, evaluate and respond to it. To protect the personal information of our Clients and end users, we cannot fulfill your request if we cannot verify your identity. You are not required to create an account with us to make a request, and we will only use the information you provide in a request to verify your identity. If you submit using an authorized agent, we will require written proof of the agent’s permission to do so and verify your identity directly with you, to the extent that we are able to identify you.

Table 5.2 below sets out are the CCPA categories of personal information collected by Simplecast from January 1, 2023:

|     |     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Category of PI collected** | **Categories of PI Sources** | **Business or Commercial Purposes for which PI is Collected** | **Categories of Third Parties to whom type of PI May Be Disclosed for a Business Purpose** | **Categories of Third Parties to whom type of PI May Be Disclosed for a Business Purpose** |
| Identifiers and Contact Information, (_such as name, address, email address, account name, account ID number, IP address,_) | • Client<br><br>• End user computer or device<br><br>• Cookies and tracking technologies | • Create and administer Client accounts<br><br>• Deliver the Services<br><br>• Improve the Services and for internal business purposes, like market research and auditing<br><br>• Understand the use of the Services, analyze trends and usage patterns,<br><br>• Determine country or state originating content requests<br><br>• Create reports on content usage for Client,<br><br>• Prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems,<br><br>• Maintain security and integrity of data and systems,<br><br>• Investigate incidents<br><br>• Contact you as a Client with messages related to the Service and account,<br><br>• Comply with policies, procedures, licenses, and legal obligations, including complying with government authority requests, regulatory requirements and enforcing our agreements and our policies<br><br>• For purposes disclosed at the time you provide your PI or otherwise with your consent | • Service provider<br><br>• Affiliated companies<br><br>• Third party analytics companies<br><br>• Third party advertising companies (Client data)<br><br>**• Third party advertising companies (End User data on Client request)**<br><br>• Third parties who may acquire your information as the result of a change of ownership<br><br>• Third parties such as government agencies as required by law or in connection with court proceedings under valid subpoena or court order | • Affiliated companies<br><br>• Third party analytics companies<br><br>• **Third party advertising entities such as ad measure-ment, reporting or attribution companies** |
| Payment Information (_such as_ _Client records, phone number, billing address, credit or debit card or other payment-related information_) | • Client | • Execute payment for Services<br><br>• Investigate and prevent fraudulent activities, violations of policy<br><br>• Maintain security and integrity of data and systems,<br><br>• Contact Client with messages related to the Service and account,<br><br>• Comply with policies, procedures, licenses, and legal obligations, including complying with government authority requests, regulatory requirements and enforcing our agreements and our policies<br><br>• For purposes disclosed at the time you provide your PI or otherwise with your consent | • Service providers<br><br>• Affiliated companies<br><br>• Third parties who may acquire your information as the result of a change of ownership<br><br>• Third parties such as government agencies as required by law or in connection with court proceedings under valid subpoena or court order | We do not sell or share this personal information |
| Commercial Information (_such as services purchased, obtained or considered_) | • Client<br><br>• Affiliated companies | • Administer your account and facilitate your access to the Services,<br><br>• Improve the Services and for internal business purposes, such as market research and auditing,<br><br>• Understand Service usage<br><br>• Maintain the security and integrity of the data and our systems,<br><br>• Identify, diagnose and address technical issues,<br><br>• Contact Client with messages related to the Service and account,<br><br>• Comply with policies, procedures, licenses, and legal obligations, including complying with government authority requests, regulatory requirements and enforcing our agreements and our policies<br><br>• For purposes disclosed at the time you provide your PI or otherwise with your consent | • Service providers<br><br>• Affiliated companie<br><br>•Third party analytics companie<br><br>•Third party advertising companies (Client data)<br><br>**• Third party advertising companies (End User data on Client request)**<br><br>• Third parties who may acquire your information as the result of a change of ownership<br><br>• Third parties such as government agencies as required by law or in connection with court proceedings under valid subpoena or court order<br><br>· | • Affiliated companies<br><br>• Third party analytics companies<br><br>**• Third party advertising entities such as ad measure-ment, reporting or attribution companies** |
| Internet or other activity information (_such as hardware model, browser, internet service provider, operating system, interactions with content on the Services_) | • Client<br><br>• Service Providers<br><br>• Affiliated companies<br><br>• Cookies and tracking technologies | • Deliver the Services<br><br>• Improve the Services and for internal business purposes, like market research and auditing<br><br>• Understand the use of the Services, analyze trends and usage patterns,<br><br>• Maintain the security and integrity of the data and our systems, investigate incidents<br><br>• Identify, diagnose and address technical issues,<br><br>• Create reports on for Client,<br><br>• Prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems,<br><br>• Contact Client with messages related to the Service and account,<br><br>• Comply with policies, procedures, licenses, and legal obligations, including complying with government authority requests, regulatory requirements and enforcing our agreements and our policies<br><br>• For purposes disclosed at the time you provide your PI or otherwise with your consent | • Service providers<br><br>• Affiliated companies<br><br>• Third party analytics companies<br><br>• Third party advertising companies (Client data)<br><br>• **Third party advertising companies (End User data on Client request)**<br><br>• Third parties who may acquire your information as the result of a change of ownership<br><br>• Third parties such as government agencies as required by law or in connection with court proceedings under valid subpoena or court order | • Affiliated companies<br><br>• Third party analytics companies<br><br>• **Third party advertising entities such as ad measure-ment, reporting or attribution companies** |
| Geolocation data (_region, country, state_) | • Client<br><br>• End user device | • Facilitate access to the Services, or to exercise territorial limits where required<br><br>• Administer the Services and account payment<br><br>• Generate service usage reports<br><br>• Investigate fraudulent activities or security threats or incidents<br><br>• Maintain the security and integrity of our data and systems<br><br>• Comply with policies, procedures and legal obligations, including governmental restrictions, regulatory requirements, and enforcing our agreement and policies<br><br>• For purposes disclosed at the time you allow the collection of geolocation or otherwise with your consent | • Service provider<br><br>• Affiliated companies<br><br>• Third party analytics companies<br><br>• Third party advertising companies (Client data)<br><br>**• Third party advertising companies (End User data on Client request)**<br><br>• Third parties who may acquire your information as the result of a change of ownership<br><br>• Third parties such as government agencies as required by law or in connection with court proceedings under valid subpoena or court order | • Affiliated companies<br><br>• Third party analytics companies<br><br>• **Third party advertising entities such as ad measure-ment, reporting or attribution companies** |

**Sale of personal data.** To the extent the definition of “sale or share” under CCPA applies to certain advertising technology collection and disclosure of personal data, such as through the use of cookies or other tracking technologies, you may opt-out of the sale or sharing with applicable law as to such activity as described in the section above titled “Use of Cookies, Pixels and Tags” and the Cookie Declaration. Simplecast does not sell personal data of Clients to third parties for their own use. Simplecast is not an advertising technology entity and does not sell or deliver advertising into the content stream. Simplecast does not sell, rent or trade personal data other than to the extent expressly described in the section above, Use of Cookies, Pixels and Tags.

**Right to non-discrimination**. You have the right to non-discriminatory treatment by us, should you exercise any of your rights.

Applicable to California residents only: Your Rights under California’s “Shine the Light” law**.** Simplecast will not provide your personal data to third parties for those third parties’ own direct marketing purposes unless we first provide you with the choice to opt-in or opt-out. If you do not opt-in or if you opt-out at the time we offer that choice, we do not share your information with that identified third party for its direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and you have questions about our practices with respect to sharing information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes and your ability to exercise choice, please write to us at: privacy@adswizz.com. We may require additional information from you to verify your identity or locate you in our system, as applicable.

1. **_Washington._** Under Washington state law, consumers have the right to know about the collection, sharing, sale, and use of health-related data about them. Simplecast does not collect, share, or sell health-related data about consumers, as defined under the Washington My Health My Data Act.

_Updated 10/18/2024_

### All plans come with a 14-day free trial  
and you can cancel anytime.

### PRODUCT

### COMPANY

### SOCIAL
